Leave the baby.
Then took this money to set up
with a man that is worthy for you.
If this what Thep's need.
I will go.
Send your child to me.
What are you going to do with my child?
You die.
Buanga, run!
I think the person you meet.
She's not a human.
Finally you come,
This necklace will protect you.
I found my mother.
I warned you, right?
Ploy,
A little more.
Are you okay?
Ploy, hang in there.
Ploy, are you okay?
Got anything?
Still can't catch the killing of Nora.
How about Khem and Buanga?
I don't know.
At the market, they say.
Lady asked the thieves
to kidnap the little girl.
The police knows.
But afraid of you therefore
they dare to do anything.
Leave the baby.
Then took this money to set up with a man that is worthy for you.
And he will only have you.
If you want me to go.
Let Thep come to talk to me.
If this is what Thep's need.
I will go.
I won't take anything.
I'll go to change clothes.
Take the baby to drink milk.
Take a bath and get ready to pick Thep up.
Duang Khae,
Yes, sir.
I know you hate Buanga.
But I don't think you are so sorrowful.
What are you talking about?
What did you do to Nora Jiam?
Do you think I did it?
When the incident happened,
I was in Hat Yai. You know that.
Yes, I know.
And isn't it a little specific?
That you had to visit a friend at that time.
Sir,
We have been together for over twenty years.
Can't you tell what kind of person I am?
It's true that you don't like Buanga.
But I can't kill anyone.
And importantly,
If I really want to do it, there won't be any suspicious behavior for anyone to catch me.
I wish you have no evidence.
Because if the police will come to arrest you.
Or take to execute.
I couldn't help you.
Who has committed a sin
and still has the nerve to blame others?
May it receive that karma.
Let it go to hell.
Don't be born again.
Thep,
Ploy,
Where is Buanga?
Let's go back and talk at home.
Just answered where Buanga?
How difficult is it?
Why do you have to go back and talk at home?
That's it.
I also want to hear from Lady's mouth.
What are you doing?
Why did Buanga and Khem have disappeared?
Since the night that Nora was dead.
Nora is dead?
Since when?
Ask your mother.
How did this happen, Mom?
The lady is not involved.
Nora is dead because of being a robber.
Buanga fled with Khem.
And leave the child here.
Mother,
It's okay.
Let me go.
Buanga,
Buanga, if someone sees us, we'll not be safe.
Even if it's a man of the lady.
Buanga,
I will go to see Thep.
Thep must protect me.
Has he ever done it?
We can secretly go to see Thep later.
How do you know that I am here?
I know that you must wait for Thep.
So I wait here every day.
If other people did it,
I'll kill them.
That's why I can't say anything.
Regardless, she is a wife.
A mother of you.
To hand her over to the police
would bring disrepute to the family.
Wait for the evidence.
I'll let the law to manage.
Khem and Buanga is a major witness.
As long as they can't find these two.
I'll not return to Bangkok.
Mother,
Hmm.
Mother, don't be suffering.
I believe the truth must appear.
Even, no one believes.
No one saw.
But God will know.
And do you believe me?
I do.
Because if your mother really
did harm the Buanga family,
You won't be suffering
because of this kind of thing.
You're the only person who believe me.
I choose the right one.
Don't leave Thep.
I won't.
Ms. Ploy,
Can you please check on the baby.
She has a fever for a few days.
Oh, dear.
I heard that some places
are getting the Spanish flu again.
Isn't this all over yet?
The infection is not severe.
But haven't gone anywhere yet.
How about?
We go to Bangkok together.
I will take the child to see the doctor at the hospital.
If she got infected, we'll get to see a doctor there.
You will also go to rest.
My baby.
Oops,
Oh,
That must be a crazy girl.
Who?
A crazy girl.
She hangs around for a few days.
When we walk to her, she'll run away.
But the people around
here are compassion, so bring her food to eat.
Where will you go?
I'll give her some money.
Oops, don't do that.
How about?
If you feel sorry for her.
I'll do it.
Yes,
- So bring me the baby.
- Yes,
Yes,
- Be careful.
- Yes,
Does it hurt?
It's not.
Wait a minute.
Here, the lady give it to you.
Take it. I'll change
my mind to keep it myself.
Oh,
You're really crazy.
This girl is so crazy.
She won't take any money.
Sir,
Will you not ask a word? Where am I going?
You were right.
Where you will go.
Ouch!
Take it later During this period,
the Lord came to me every night.
Who?
Hurry and catch it.
It can pass through the fence as fast as it disappears.
They know the way.
Found Mr. Thep?
Please take card of the baby.
Don't worry.
I'll take good care of her.
I'll go to send you.
I don't want you to go.
Afraid that you will never come back again.
She probably has been
waiting today for a long time.
The day you don't have to wear a mask.
You know everything.
If we meet again,
I will tell you everything I have done.
Back off.
Yes,
But if you are good,
Your people would not have become mine.
I'll hurry to send the news back.
- Be safe.
- Yes.
Safe travel.
Let's go inside.
What are you going to eat today?
Let's go, mom.
I'll talk to her.
Please don't.
Nevermind.
I'll handle this.
Sister,
What do you want?
Ouch!
Let me go.
My baby.
Go away.
Don't mess with my child.
I said go.
I will have to become a nun.
Or made a big merit.
It's my fault.
I shouldn't trust other people.
Walked in, even though
we didn't even know each other.
With people we know well.
It's not that we can always trust.
Thep didn't come.
He said that if he didn't see Buanga and Thep, he would not return to Bangkok.
Believe me.
Thep,
My people say that they
meet someone look like Kem.
Come to hang around
at the train station many days ago.
Dad,
Where are you?
I've no one.
My people say that
they met someone like Kem,
Hang around at the train
station many days ago.
What did you do?
Kem and Buanga have disappeared
since the night that Nora was dead.
When did Nora die?
Ask your mother.
I would like to curse everyone.
That makes me lost everything.
May it and all its kin be destroyed.
Regardless of any life.
I would like to follow.
Even its spirit.
There will be no hell to support.
Let it perish.
Ruin.
Forever.
Why did you do this?
Why?
Help me.
Can you help me?
Go away.
Don't mess with my child.
I said go.
Buanga,
The person who made me to be here.
Then must die here.
But it's myself.
Duang Khae,
Now I know the truth
on the day that is too late.
Lord Decha.
I ordered again and again.
That today will go to make merit.
No one woke up.
Yeah, let it be like this.
Please cook a rice.
I will go to hit the guys ...
Oh, I'm scared. Rest in peace Buanga.
Phorn, the closest
servant of Duang Khae was die.
There is no trace of whoever did it.
And no one believes
that she killed herself.
Everyone said...
Buanga killed her.
What's wrong?
Phorn is die.
She hate Buanga.
People say that.
Buanga killed her.
Mother,
The ghost kills people.
There are only novels.
And importantly,
You didn't hurt Buanga and her father.
Why would she come to avenge?
Yes,
But I did bad thing to her.
I'm afraid.
Ploy,
Can't you go to work tonight?
I couldn't.
I will let my friend come to be with you.
How are you?
Mother,
And then there's Duang Khae
who doesn't get along with Buanga.
Came to die mysterious.
The forensic doctor concluded
that Duang Kae had a heart attack.
But like everyone is willing to believe that.
Because of the vengeance of Buanga.
Ploy,
If I'm not here,
You can take care of the child, right?
Why do you ask?
Saw the people around me die like this.
I feel that my life is uncertain.
I can take care of Chan.
But it's better if you stay with us.
Chan didn't have mother.
She should have father.
I want you to bring the child
to Bangkok as soon as possible.
How about you?
I have an important business to do.
You ask me to go away.
I really love you.
Then die for me.
Thep, don't.
It's not your business.
Chan, you go with me.
This child has never been your child.
This man is not your husband.
I won't let you guys take
my child away from me again.
A strange event happened
since I found that house.
It's my fault for insisting on staying here.
I know the reason.
You must die.